{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_15_CISDAW",
                "player_4_CISDAW",
                "player_16_CISDAW",
                "player_5_CISDAW",
                "player_3_CISDAW",
                "player_6_CISDAW"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                15,
                4,
                16,
                5,
                3,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "stand",
                "pick_up",
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -58736.816,
                    77053.919,
                    -6236.641,
                    0,
                    -89.53809779861146,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -58706.598,
                    76754.387,
                    -6221.251,
                    0,
                    -116.25831707700908,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -58772.002,
                    77327.473,
                    -6234.987,
                    0.0,
                    -90.003,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -58856.816,
                    76863.953,
                    -6226.301,
                    0.0,
                    -90.001,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -59211.537,
                    77217.237,
                    -6192.985,
                    0,
                    -110.34043874718986,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -58556.943,
                    76545.971,
                    -6209.302,
                    0,
                    -105.36730247238293,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -58320.467,
            76538.927,
            -6224.149
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1320.3041532976642
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -58395.31,
            76113.221,
            -6218.844,
            0,
            115.90352358399508,
            0
        ],
        [
            -58111.182,
            76670.881,
            -6263.468,
            0,
            157.39588039967498,
            0
        ],
        [
            -59199.093,
            77611.157,
            -6187.777,
            0,
            -58.91293296779792,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "six"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many male figures can be seen among the figures?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the total number of women in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene have a bald head?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many figures are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many figures are lying motionless on the ground?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "five"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding something",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding something"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-neck top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouching"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouching"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}